What? We're moving?
Two weeks from now?
Hmm?
Okay.
What's wrong, Taka?
You've been acting weird lately.
We need to talk.
About what?
It's big, but I want to tell you tomorrow.
We can meet back here if that's cool with you.
Yeah, I'm totally fine with that.
Honestly, there's something I've been meaning to tell you, too.
Tomorrow, then.
I wanted to tell him in two days I was going to be moving away.
But the next day I waited until the sun went down.
He never showed up.
So I left.
I ended up leaving without ever saying goodbye to my only friend.
Crazy dream.
What's she doing in here?
Huh?
What was I dreaming about again?
Oh, voice is a little girl!
Huh?
Oh, boy, look.
Oh, boy.
Oh, man.
Oh, boy, oh, boy.
Oh, boy.
has this semester gone by crazy fast to you guys too or is that just me yeah summer vacation
starts tomorrow weird as you know the neighbors club exists for one reason only and that's to
make friends now is anyone here made even one friend anyone have fun-filled summer plans with
said new friends actually for me I think my rep's worse now than it was before I joined me too
earlier I heard some girls talking about me and they said you know Senna is totally dating that
blonde thug how they could even believe that much less repeat it is beyond me I should punch their
faces off yeah that sucks I'm sorry no you don't have to apologize because they are stupid what
kind of club activities have you all been doing so far have they helped you make new friends well
let me think about it we played some video games and that's all we practiced role-playing with video
games so for the most part you've just been fooling around hey I have a question have any of you ever
been to one of those karaoke box things like where you can rent your own private karaoke room yeah I've
been to what why are you both so surprised it's hard to imagine you singing karaoke that's all
whatever I may not look like it to you freaks but I'll have you know I've been to all the
karaoke boxes in the city wow that seems excessive and sad why would you go to every single one by
yourself who said I was by myself jack wagon karaoke boxes are obviously places you go with friends what
singing karaoke with your friends is fun hello not only does Tomo have an amazing voice she is like
beyond supportive when you're singing sometimes she'll even sing backup right forgot about her Tomo the air
friend why are you looking at me like that no reason no reason at all so both of them have been
karaoke-ing before Senna have you never been to one oh yeah no who cares though I put the class in
class II so why would I do something so unsophisticated give me some credit I would never do that like
ever I may not have ever been invited to go but I was fine because I didn't want to easy no one said
you wanted to Kodaka Rika has never been to karaoke but Rika would very much like to go along Rika imagines
it would be rather difficult to go into a place like that all alone perhaps next time you would consider
taking Rika to karaoke with you sure sounds good to me really thank you wait I'm here too plus if
you want to know the best place to go you should stick with me that's nice of you to offer thanks
Yosara excuse me I've never been to one of those karaoke box places either all of this talking about
singing has put me in the mood to perform Chaos Requiem well when do you want to go no one has anything to
do tomorrow do they I suppose I could make time to go after noonish Rika's available all day long so
is Yukimura tomorrow it is then when and where should we meet up my favorite karaoke box is a 10 minute
walk from the Toyonishi station cool then let's meet in front of the ticket gates at the station perfect
what time wait hold on just a second cuz I um you um what meat at the moment we're trying to make plans
to go to a karaoke box together you know the unsophisticated disgusting place your classy lady
lumps wouldn't be caught dead in don't tell me you've changed your mind and want to go with us
look lumpy unless you're a wealth of karaoke info you're interrupting a conversation that has nothing
at all to do with you so why don't you take a seat and shut up for once no I'm not the place I'm
thinking of is free playtime tomorrow it starts at 1 so why don't we all meet up then make sure you eat
lunch before you go stop ignoring me oh I'm sorry I just assumed you were telling the truth when you
said you didn't want to go with us but obviously you were lying way to put the ass in class I wasn't
lying hey we don't care either way so if you want to go go come on admit it you want to don't you um yes I do I
I I want to go I can't hear you I I want to go to I'm sorry what was that I said I want to go with
you guys to karaoke I see well I can certainly understand that but the reality is I don't
really want you to go with us although I suppose I can make an exception all you have to do is beg
what bag just say please take me with you put some heart into it please take me with you I would
appreciate it please take me with you you know what I couldn't hear you like at all and don't
forget the most important part is the begging part would you get Rika another cup of coffee
louder saggy bags you need to start begging like you mean it okay fine I'm officially begging please
let me go too that wasn't so hard huh but still no what do I have to do you harpy I'm going whether
you like it or not plus why would I need your permission to go anywhere in the first place
took you long enough to realize that guy you really are mentally challenged aren't you
now that she's gone you guys want to go ahead and decide on the real time in place we should meet
are you like the devil it was just a joke I have an appointment tomorrow at 1 so I will need to have
lunch prepared early appointment would that be with those friends of yours no of course it's not
it's with the neighbor's club if I don't go they'll be lost without me it's tragic really
what is the club planning to do karaoke I'm going to ambush Shioza Brett and Kodaka with my gorgeous
gorgeous singing voice I also really want to do a duet with Kobito she's adorable did you say Kodaka
why are you wearing that today aren't you on fire a true air of the night tribe transcends even the
hottest of heat I doubt she even knows what that means look they're all here last but not least are
you ready why are you guys so early we've still got 10 minutes before one I wasn't first I got here
five minutes after Rika did well I only arrived 20 minutes before you did because I'm your sidekick
Rika managed to beat Senna to our meeting place by 15 minutes but I was still here 15 minutes before
Yukimura why are you guys talking like you're in the middle of some math word problem okay try to
figure out who got here at what time based upon what they all just said come on it'll be fun for you
now we arrived at exactly 12 50 you have until we get to the karaoke place to answer you forget all
I need to do is access the Akashic records and solving a problem like this one shall be a breeze
watch and learn mere mortal why do you have to use the powers of darkness on everything oh yeah we
almost there shut up yes we are so what's the name of this place anyway oh it's cry from the abyss that
doesn't make Rika feel safe run Taka what's taking so long wait for me how are you so bad Kodaka what the
hell good afternoon wow we're actually at a karaoke box drink bar and free time one sec there are
six of you total is that right huh oh yeah six total all righty then the total for free time and
drinks for six people is 5400 yen well free time for one person is 650 and the drink bar is 250 so
that's nine per person that's a lot just so I'm clear on this isn't that right that's what you
said isn't it hey what's wrong the total doesn't make sense why what do you mean the price for the
drink bar is pretty much the only thing that does make sense get this we're only using one room but
they want to charge each of us to use it is that not normal meat what do you go to a karaoke box to
do well um to sing some songs right exactly it's still one room whether one person sings 30 songs or
six people sing five it's 30 songs total regardless so why do we have to pay six times as much for what we
could get cheaper on our own so basically it's a scam yeah I think that's their game you know it's
like really weird they never charged me twice when I came here with Tomo are you insane she's not real
why would they charge her besides that all karaoke boxes charge per person it's perfectly normal no way
it's definitely a scam I don't want to but I have to agree my daddy said to me once people who know
better should never overlook the unnatural movement of money so I know exactly what we should do about
this hey not bad for a flotation device thanks you can forget what I said about six people the usual
I'm going to want free time and drinks in my own room I'm acquainted with these people but I'm not
actually here with them we just walked in at the same time oh okay one person it is then hey dude
this is my very first time I want to get free time and drinks for only me thanks that's weird what are
they doing rika supposes they want us each to have our own singing room aren't they kind of missing the
point of us coming together great same price for you then focus Kodaka it's your turn we're gonna go on
ahead so are you by yourself as well no four please four people in just one room are you sure yeah four
thank you so much sir that's cool right yes let's sing a duet I don't care as long as I'm in the same
room that you are I believe it's time for you to finally hear my rock star voice wonderful I need to
make a member card for you real quick cool thanks is everything all right yeah everything is perfect
will that be cash or credit oh cash please you should go first Kodaka Rika wants to hear what you sound
like me give me just a minute come on and load the room full of your awesome juices Rika gross Rika's
putting this large hard black thing right here stop just call it a mic
here I go go Kodaka how can I believe in my reality when everything I see is so sublime to me this is the life you knew the one you spoke of so many questions start to burn and turn inside my hair and I know it's hard for us to speak when all I've done is neglect you
that was great I didn't know you had such a wonderful voice it really was the most beautiful thing
Rika thinks she might be wet this reminds me of the time when we went running through the moonless night
together seven years ago really because I don't remember that I wonder if the girls are singing now
too all alone did you like my loving up the microphone finish did you feel a tingle absolutely
not huh Rika spent all night working on it though I'm up next and I'm dedicating this song to you big
brother that's nice well have at it Yukimura I wonder if I went in their rooms to hear them if
they'd get pissed off at me get out they have my favorite song ever that's fantastic
when you feel so alone
I hope you mortals are ready for this
rain is falling and every dream of us starts to fade the memories are all we have now we have
something a friendship that could last through the bad and good but then you walked away
The day you turned your back on me
There are no words that I could say
To keep you here with me
And it hurts to know you would ever leave
All I needed was your sympathy
I was living in a fantasy
But it's over now
Cause I set you free
My throat hurts from all the singing
Kodaka, hearing your voice so low is driving Rika wild
It's super sadistic and sexy all at the same time
Rika's correct, it's giving me chills as well
Huh? Hey, what's wrong with you guys?
Why don't you ask fog lights?
Whatever, she so started it
I'm guessing this had something to do with singing
You know how there's a mode that scores you?
I was using that the whole time
And it ranked all of the rooms
When I started singing, the name Night was disgustingly all over the top rankings
Since that describes her soul, I figured it was Yozara
I was trying to fill up all the slots with my name
Until Senna the Gross just had to show up
Unwanted and ruin everything as usual
Because that's what she does
Seriously? You were in separate rooms and still fighting?
So then who ended up with the highest rank?
Me, obviously
What are you talking about? I had the top score at 99
Like that means anything
I totally dominated ranks 2 through 11 with a 98 on every one
Who cares? First place is first place
On top of winning first, I had more 97s than you did
Liar! Evil must be eating your brain because I had like way more 97s
Just cause you say it doesn't make it true
Whatever, you wouldn't know the truth if it hit me
That was really fun, wasn't it? We should totally do it again
Yeah
Thank you for coming
I guess this is our last club activity for the semester
Oh yeah, I guess
Does that mean Rika has to wait 40 days before she can fool around with you again?
Stop doing that, Rika
We haven't fooled around at all, so quit acting like we have
Looks like I won't get to be your gopher for a really long time then
Geez, what the hell are you all freaking out about?
The club's not going to take a break for the summer
What? We're not taking a break?
Is there a reason for that?
All of the other clubs at school are still going to meet over the summer
So why would we be any different?
To start out, summer is the normal kids' most social time of the entire year
It wouldn't make sense for us not to meet since our goal is to make friends with them
We also need to keep up with our training
We don't want to forget what we've already learned
It's like the logic of pouring boiling water into a glass that isn't used so it cracks, right?
Sure, whatever you say
Isn't that thermal expansion?
Our next official meeting will be on Monday
Each of you needs to be prepared to discuss why you haven't been able to make friends so far
What is it, twins?
The answer to your question is you
You're a terrible leader and that's why we've all failed
You know, now that you bring it up, I have a couple of answers myself
First of all, you are the most worthless person I have ever met
Not to mention lame and beyond stupid
Between your tiny brain and your incompetence when trying to accomplish anything
Your existence to the club, technically to the world
Is meaningless
You are so rude
You're right, I said too much
Which is funny when you think about it
Because there aren't enough words to describe how much of a hazardous waste of a person you are
You really suck
Should we leave them?
We should, yes
Are you sure?
Don't stop walking
I understand, sir
I'd call you a pit of raw food
But that would be giving you too much credit
Everyone's looking
And I'm not willing to do that
Shut up!
No more!
Yozara, you're such an evil
I hate you, I wish you'd die
That dumb girl is so dramatic, it's disgusting
It's been a month since the club started
And none of it would have happened without her
Hey, Yozara
Hmm?
This past month, it's been a whole lot of fun
Thank you
Whatevs
Hey, Kodika!
Wait!
What's up?
I forgot to tell you something
I was talking to Daddy yesterday
He said he had some free time over the summer
You can come over and see him whenever
I guess he's been wanting to meet you too
No way, really?
I'll make sure to come by soon
Just let me know beforehand, cool?
Sure
Wait, slow your roll
Why the hell would he go over to your house?
And on top of that, why would he ever need to meet your father?
Hmm
Well, actually, it's because
Kodika!
I think you should keep that a secret
You don't want it to cause any trouble
Yeah, that's a good point
I'm sorry, Senna
She's right
It's probably best not to advertise the president of the school used his authority to make sure the new thug got accepted
So what kind of secret is this?
The kind of secret that has absolutely nothing to do with you
Whatever reason he has to come over to my house
And or visit with my father
Well, those are his reasons
And he doesn't have to explain them to anyone
Bye, kids
I'll see you soon, Kodika
K
Oh, Kodaka, Rika is so happy she gets to see you over the summer break.
I'm really excited I get to see you, too.
Don't you guys have anything exciting planned, though?
Do you have exciting plans?
No, not exactly.
Rika knew it! You know what we should do, then?
Curvy stuff! With each other!
Never fear, big brother. For the next 40 days, I'll be at your beck and call.
Come on.
Next, my cell phone doesn't get many calls.
Hey, where did he go?
And here we are with no way of contacting him.
So I'm going to end here.
I'll give you a call.
It should be a car sound.
After all, I'm from this, and the pont William Rain security guy may not be ..
I'd shut your back up and talk to his hand.
Yes?
I would love to make over to him.
Yeah?
I think right.
Well, here are some of my nether Correo's floppy chưa.
I'd cut an arrow here and пис down on your hand.
No?
No way.
Yes?